{
    "subject": "resource/Fatty's_Chance_Acquaintance",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is a film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.916975736618042,
            "question": "Who might have starred in 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149836897850037,
            "question": "Are there any similar films to 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8807435631752014,
            "question": "Could 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance' be a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8377415537834167,
            "question": "What might the plot of 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance' involve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7955464720726013,
            "question": "What impact did 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance' have on film history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7480195164680481,
            "question": "Is 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance' a fictional story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6690939664840698,
            "question": "What type of work is 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.665855348110199,
            "question": "Has 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance' been remade or adapted?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6585080623626709,
            "question": "Where might one find information about 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4549470841884613,
            "question": "What decade was 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance' likely released in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is a film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7155_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might one find information about 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7155_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance' been remade or adapted?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7155_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is 'Fatty's Chance Acquaintance'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7155_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7155_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents clearly states that \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance\" is a Keystone Film, and the context provided (the mention of American silent film actor Roscoe 'Fatty' Arbuckle) supports the conclusion that it is indeed a film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance (1915), by Keystone\" and provide details about the film, including its director, actors, and production information. This clearly indicates that \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance\" is a film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}